propgod.com 2015-03-19

# Privacy | Propgod

www.PropGod.com (henceforth called PropGod) is an internet portal wholly owned, operated and managed by PropGod Services Private Limited. 

PropGod respects the privacy of it is users and is committed to protect it in all respects. With a view to offer most enriching and holistic internet experience to users, PROPGOD offers a vast repository of internet technology enabled features and variety of community services. The information about the user as collected by PROPGOD is:   
(a) information supplied by users and (b) information automatically tracked while navigation (Information). 

By using PROPGOD's website or its services, you consent to collection, storage, and use of the personal information you provide (including any changes thereto as provided by you) for any of the services that we offer.

### USER INFORMATION 

To avail certain sites / services on our websites, users may be required to provide certain information for the registration process namely:-   
a) name, b) email address c) password etc., and / or your occupation, interests, and the like.. The Information as supplied by the users enables us to improve our sites and provide you the most user-friendly experience. None of this information is shared to anyone other than whom it is intended to at any point of time without your permission. 

All required information is service dependent and PROPGOD may use the above said User information to, maintain, protect, and improve its services (including advertising services) and for developing new services

Such information will not be considered as sensitive if it is freely available and accessible in the public domain or is furnished under the Right to Information Act, 2005 or any other law for the time being in force. 

### COOKIES

To improve the responsiveness of the sites for our users, we may use "cookies", or similar electronic tools to collect information to assign each visitor a unique, random number as a User Identification (User ID) to understand the user's individual interests using the Identified Computer. Unless you voluntarily identify yourself (through registration, for example), we will have no way of knowing who you are, even if we assign a cookie to your computer. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply (an example of this is when you ask for our Personalised Horoscope). A cookie cannot read data off your hard drive. Our advertisers may also assign their own cookies to your browser (if you click on their ads), a process that we do not control. 

Our web servers automatically collect limited information about your computer's connection to the Internet, including your IP address, when you visit our site. (Your IP address is a number that lets computers attached to the Internet know where to send you data -- such as the web pages you view.) Your IP address does not identify you personally. We use this information to deliver our web pages to you upon request, to tailor our site to the interests of our users, to measure traffic within our site and let advertisers know the geographic locations from where our visitors come. 

### LINK TO THIRD PARTY SITES

PROPGOD may include links to other websites. Such sites are governed by their respective privacy policies, which are beyond our control. Once you leave our servers (you can tell where you are by checking the URL in the location bar on your browser), use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the site you are visiting. That policy may differ from ours. If you can't find the privacy policy of any of these sites via a link from the site's homepage, you should contact the site directly for more information. 

When we present information to our advertisers -- to help them understand our audience and confirm the value of advertising on our website -- it is usually in the form of aggregated statistics on traffic to various pages within our site. When you register with PROPGOD, we contact you from time to time about updation of your content to provide the users such features that we believe may benefit you. You may however opt out of these services at your wish. 

### INFORMATION SHARING

PROPGOD shares the sensitive personal information to any third party without obtaining the prior consent of the User in the following limited circumstances:

**a)** When it is requested or required by law or by any court or governmental agency or authority to disclose, for the purpose of verification of identity, or for the prevention, detection, investigation including cyber incidents, or for prosecution and punishment of offences. These disclosures are made in good faith and belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary for enforcing these Terms; for complying with the applicable laws and regulations. 

b) PROPGOD proposes to share such information within its group companies and officers and employees of such group companies for the purpose of processing personal information on its behalf. We also ensure that these recipients of such information agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. 

### ACCESSING AND UPDATING PERSONAL INFORMATION 

When you use PROPGOD's websites, we make good faith efforts to provide you, as and when requested by you, with access to your personal information and shall further ensure that any personal information or sensitive personal data or information found to be inaccurate or deficient shall be corrected or amended as feasible, subject to any requirement for such personal information or sensitive personal data or information to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. We ask individual users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes), or for which access is not otherwise required. In any case where we provide information access and correction, we perform this service free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort. Because of the way we maintain certain services, after you delete your information, residual copies may take a period of time before they are deleted from our active servers and may remain in our backup systems. 

### INFORMATION SECURITY 

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, including appropriate encryption and physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data. 

All information gathered on PROPGOD is securely stored within the PROPGOD controlled database. The database is stored on servers secured behind a firewall; access to the servers is password-protected and is strictly limited. However, as effective as our security measures are, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet. And, of course, any information you include in a posting to the discussion areas is available to anyone with Internet access. 

However the internet is an ever evolving medium. We may change our privacy policy from time to time to incorporate necessary future changes. Of course, our use of any information we gather will always be consistent with the policy under which the information was collected, regardless of what the new policy may be. 

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Any complaints or concerns with regards to content or to report any abuse of laws or breach of these terms may be taken up with the designated grievance redressal officer as mentioned below via post or by sending an email to [info@propgod.com.](mailto:info@propgod.com)

### Grievance Redressal

Redressal Mechanism: Any complaints, abuse or concerns with regards to content and or comment or breach of these terms shall be immediately informed to the designated Grievance Officer as mentioned below via in writing or through email signed with the electronic signature to [info@propgod.com.](mailto:info@propgod.com)

www.propgod.com

PropGod Services Pvt Ltd  
Shanti -1, #001, Ground Floor,  
Sai Gardens, Kadugodi-Hoskote Road,  
Seegahalli, Bangalore – 560067.  
Ph: 080 – 4954 6095.

We request you to please provide the following information in your complaint:-  
(a) A physical or electronic signature of a person authorized to act on behalf of the copyright owner for the purposes of the complaint.  
(b) Identification of the copyrighted work claimed to have been infringed.  
(c) Identification of the material on our website that is claimed to be infringing or to be the subject of infringing activity.   
(d) The address, telephone number or e-mail address of the complaining party.  
(e) A statement that the complaining party has a good-faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent or the law.  
(f) A statement, under penalty of perjury, that the information in the notice of copyright infringement is accurate, and that the complaining party is authorized to act on behalf of the owner of the right that is allegedly infringed.  

www.propgod.com All trademarks, logos and names are properties of their respective owners. All Rights Reserved.© Copyright 2014 PropGod Services Private Limited Terms of use
